var questions = [
	{
		question: "What do reptiles and amphibians have in common?",
		answers:
					{
						a: "invertebrates",
						b: "live only in water",
						c: "live only on land",
						d: "vertebrates"
					},
		correct_answer: "d"
	},
	{
		question: "What do a cat, a turtle, and a gold fish have in common?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "all are vertebrates",
				b: "all have gills",
				c: "all have leaves",
				d: "all have lungs"
			},
		correct_answer: "a"
	},
	{
		question: "What do a humming bird, a crocodile, a fish, and a tree frog have in common?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "hey all have slimy skin",
				b: "they all have wings",
				c: "they all lay eggs",
				d: "they all live on land"
			},
		correct_answer: "c"
	},
	{
		question: "Which of the following is not a characteristic of an animal that is classified as an amphibian?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "adults live on land and breathe with lungs",
				b: "they all have wings",
				c: "they have backbones",
				d: "they have many cells"
			},
		correct_answer: "b"
	},
	{
		question: "Which characteristics do a newt, a bull frog, and a salamander have in common?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "all are warm-blooded reptiles",
				b: "all are cold-blooded amphibians",
				c: "all are cold-blooded reptiles",
				d: "all are warm-blooded amphibians"
			},
		correct_answer: "b"
	},
	{
		question: "Which of the following describes the  characteristics of arthropods?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "Warm-blooded, moist skin, exoskeleton",
				b: "Warm-blooded, dry skin, internal skeleton",
				c: "Exoskeleton, jointed appendages, segmented body",
				d: "Exoskeleton, joined appendages, solid body"
			},
		correct_answer: "c"
	},
	{
		question: "Which animal is a mammal that lives in the ocean?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "Whale",
				b: "Seahorse",
				c: "Fish",
				d: "Shark"
			},
		correct_answer: "a"
	},
	{
		question: "Which category of plants do mosses and liverworts belong to?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "vascular plants",
				b: "non-vascular plants",
				c: "angiosperms",
				d: "gymnosperms"
			},
		correct_answer: "b"
	},
	{
		question: "Which of the vertebrates below are cold-blooded?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "amphibians and fish",
				b: "amphibians and birds",
				c: "mammals and birds",
				d: "mammals and fish"
			},
		correct_answer: "a"
	},
	{
		question: "How are arthropods classified?",
		answers:
			{
				a: "Vertebrates",
				b: "Invertebrates",
				c: "Fish",
				d: "Amphibians"
			},
		correct_answer: "b"
	}
];
